https://flitwickmotorcycles.co.uk/home/privacy-policy-2/

Privacy Policy
HomeHome Privacy Policy
Who we are
Our website address is: https://flitwickmotorcycles.co.uk.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymised string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Contact us forms are at the bottom of each page on this site.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
We use general analytics to see what type of vistors we have, but these are not specific to any individual.
Who we share your data with
We do not share your data submitted to this site with any third party. We store, on a secure site through the company MAIL CHIMP, accessible only by authorized and trained members of staff details entered by those that have chosen to opt in or subscribe to our newsletters.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognise and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
We can be contacted at by post to Flitwick Motorcycles, Station Road, Flitwick, Bedford, MK45 1JR, by email to website@flitwickmotorcycles.co.uk or use the contact us tab.
Additional information
How we protect your data
Your Data is securely held on password protected and virus protected servers.
What data breach procedures we have in place
We scan our systems regularly, do not print or save personal data without permission, and have a robust reporting process in place.
What third parties we receive data from
Wwe do not receive data from third parties in connection with the use of this site.
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
We do not profiling on this site.
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
Our data processor officer and data controller is Carole Linsdell, Flitwick Motorcycles, Station Road, Flitwick, Bedford MK45 1JR
Newsletter
By subscribing to our newsletter you will always be up-to-date on our latest promotions, deals, news and events!
Email address:
Leave this field empty if you're human:
Bedfordshires Exclusive Premier Yamaha Dealers
Contact Us
Address:Flitwick Motorcycles, Station Road, Flitwick, Bedfordshire MK45 1JR, UK
Phone:01525 712197
Email:flitwick@flitwickmotorcycles.co.uk
